Guide to the Anaconda Copper Mining Company records 1876-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Boston and Montana Consolidated Copper and Silver Mining Company / Reduction Department (Great Falls)
  - Subject File
    - #1013 Butte Reduction Works: concentrator, 1910-1911, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 237 / 10)
    - #1014 "Elevators: construction and installation of concentrator elevators", 1910-1920 (Box-folder 237 / 11)
    - #1015 "Power requirements for Electrolytic Department", 1917-1931 (Box-folder 237 / 12)
    - #1016 "Converter linings: basic linings, 1901-1911 (Box-folder 237 / 13)
    - #1017 "Mammoth Milling and Mining Company: concentrator machinery for sale", 1910 (Box-folder 237 / 14)
    - #1018 "Production: instructions from United Metals Selling Company...", 1908-1948 (Box-folder 237 / 15)
    - #1019 "Weighing of converter charges", 1910-1914 (Box-folder 237 / 16)
    - #1020-1024 "Stationery (samples), 1907-1914 (Box-folder 237 / 17)
    - #1025 "Fluxing values and cost of limestone", 1904-1927 (Box-folder 237 / 18)
    - #1025-2 "Fluxing values and cost of limestone: shipments of limestone to Holly Sugar Company", 1925-1935 (Box-folder 237 / 19)
    - #1025-3 "Fluxing values and cost of limestone: shipments of limestone to Utah-Idaho Company", 1939-1942 (Box-folder 237 / 20)
    - #1027 "Marine insurance", 1908-1924 (Box-folder 238 / 1)
    - #1028 "Welding", 1913-1953 (Box-folder 238 / 2)
    - #1029 "Fine crushing", 1910-1950 (Box-folder 238 / 3)
    - #1030 "Jones and Laughlin contract for erection of steel work...on dust chamber & flues" (re stack), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 238 / 4)
    - #1030-5 "Jones and Laughlin contract ...reports" (re stack), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 238 / 5)
    - #1031 "John L. Mullan contracts...on dust chambers & flues" (re stack), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 238 / 6)
    - #1032 "Brickwork in flues and dust chambers" (re stack), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 238 / 7)
    - #1032-3,4,5 "Brickwork in flues and dust chambers: Alphons Custodis" (re stack), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 238 / 8)
    - #1033 "Custodis brick plant" (re stack), 1907-1908 (Box-folder 238 / 9)
    - #1034-1 "B & M brick plant: leasing", 1909-1910 (Box-folder 238 / 10)
    - #1034-2 "B & M brick plant: lease to Coombs and King" (includes tests on disintegration of brick in Rainbow Hotel), 1909-1910 (Box-folder 238 / 11-13)
    - #1034 [ Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1909-1910 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - #1034-7,8 "B & M brick plant: price, shipment", 1910 (Box-folder 238 / 14)
    - #1036 "Brick Department costs", 1910-1932 (Box-folder 239 / 1)
    - #1037 "Manufacture of building bricks", 1909-1927 (Box-folder 239 / 2)
    - #1038 "Manufacture of reverberatory bricks", 1911-1935 (Box-folder 239 / 3)
    - #1039 "Manufacture of brick for miscellaneous purposes", 1905-1935 (Box-folder 239 / 4)
    - #1040 "B & M Brick Plant" (re clay and shale supply), 1916-1925 (Box-folder 239 / 5)
    - #1041 "B & M Brick Plant" (re improvements, consolidation with Anaconda Brick Plant), 1910-1911 (Box-folder 239 / 6)
    - #1041 "B & M Brick Plant" (re improvements, consolidation with Anaconda Brick Plant) [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1910-1911 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - #1042 "Brick Plant production", 1910-1939 (Box-folder 239 / 7)
    - #1043 "Power rates", 1909-1950 (Box-folder 239 / 8)
    - #1043 "Power installations" (includes Niagara Falls Power Company and Ontario Power Company brochures), 1908 (Box-folder 239 / 9)
    - #1044 "Computation of power consumption: Black Eagle and Rainbow dams", 1899-1920 (Box-folder 239 / 10)
    - #1045-1048 "Increase and remodelling of Great Falls plant": estimates #1-5, 1906-1911 (Box-folder 239 / 11-14)
    - # 1047, 1048 "Increase and remodelling of Great Falls plant": estimates #1-5 [ Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1906-1911 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - #1049 "Increase and remodelling of Great Falls plant": estimate #6, 1910-1916 (Box-folder 240 / 1-2)
    - #1050 "Furnace bottoms", 1898-1959 (Box-folder 240 / 3)
    - #1051 "Slime ponds", 1910-1952 (Box-folder 240 / 4)
    - #1052 "Weighing machines and calculators", 1910-1911 (Box-folder 240 / 5)
    - #1053 "Mine water: precipitation of copper", 1904-1936 (Box-folder 240 / 6)
    - #1054 "Rules governing the giving out of information", 1901-1966 (Box-folder 240 / 7)
    - #1055 "Roasting furnaces", 1921-1955 (Box-folder 240 / 8)
    - #1056 "Average assays on concentrator product", 1911-1914 (Box-folder 240 / 9)
    - #1060 "Roads and road building", 1910-1964 (Box-folder 240 / 10)
    - #1061 "Roasting furnaces" (includes patents), 1902-1964 (Box-folder 240 / 11)
    - #1062 "McDougall furnaces", 1900-1951 (Box-folder 240 / 12)
    - #1063 "McDougall flue dust and dust prevention", 1902-1912 (Box-folder 241 / 1)
    - #1064 "Construction, installation and repairs of McDougall furnaces", 1902-1963 (Box-folder 241 / 2)
    - #1065-1 "Chimney flues and dust chambers: temperatures..." [re stack], 1910-1951 (Box-folder 241 / 3)
    - #1065-2 "Chimney flues and dust chambers: gases in reverberatory flue and main dust chamber" [re stack], 1910-1934 (Box-folder 241 / 4)
    - #1065-3,5 "Chimney flues and dust chambers" (re leakage, zinc plant dryer stack), 1914, 1948 (Box-folder 241 / 5)
    - #1065-4 "Chimney flues and dust chambers" (re stack), 1917-1957 (Box-folder 241 / 6-7)
    - #1066 "Richards' pulsator classifiers: official test results", 1907-1913 (Box-folder 242 / 1-2)
    - #1067 "Richards' single pocket classifiers", 1910-1928 (Box-folder 242 / 3)
    - #1068 Metallurgical tables, 1911-1914 (Box-folder 242 / 4)
    - #1069 Reverberatory furnaces, 1901-1948 (Box-folder 242 / 5-6)
    - #1070 "Disposition of flue dust: treatment of arsenical flue dust in Reverberatory furnaces", 1910-1917 (Box-folder 242 / 7)
    - #1071 Hancock jigs, 1910-1912 (Box-folder 243 / 1-3)
    - #1072 Wilfley tables, 1910-1912 (Box-folder 243 / 4)
    - #1073 Vanners, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 243 / 5)
    - #1074 Deslimers, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 243 / 6)
    - #1079 "Construction and installation of smelter buildings, additions, & bins", 1909-1910 (Box-folder 243 / 7)
    - #1080 "Class V converters & stalls", 1911-1942 (Box-folder 243 / 8)
    - #1081 Mining costs, 1911-1961 (Box-folder 243 / 9)
    - #1085 Safety First Department, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 243 / 10-11)
    - #1085 Safety First Department, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 244 / 1-7)
    - #1085 Safety First Department, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 245 / 1-2)
    - #1085 Safety First Department (miscellaneous sub-files), 1916-1970 (Box-folder 245 / 3)
    - #1085-8 Safety First Department: safety committees and meetings, 1914-1964 (Box-folder 245 / 4)
    - #1085 Safety First Department (miscellaneous sub-files), 1922-1957 (Box-folder 245 / 5)
    - #1085-11 Safety First Department: U.S. Bureau of Mines rescue car and first aid training, 1916-1960 (Box-folder 245 / 6)
    - #1085-14 Safety First Department: health and safety in Great Falls Department, 1956 (Box-folder 245 / 7)
    - #1085-14 Safety First Department: industrial hygiene, 1944-1951 (Box-folder 246 / 1-6)
    - #1085-14 Safety First Department: industrial hygiene, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 247 / 1-6)
    - #1085-14 Safety First Department: industrial hygiene, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 248 / 1-4)
    - #1085-15 Safety First Department: safety awards, 1939-1959 (Box-folder 248 / 5)
    - #1085 Safety First Department: reports, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 248 / 6)
    - #1085 Safety First Department: reports, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 249 / 1)
    - #1086 Laboratory Department: metallurgical lab, 1908-1958 (Box-folder 249 / 2)
    - #1087 Testing Department, 1911-1935 (Box-folder 249 / 3)
    - #1088 Arizona Copper Company: Hancock jigs, etc., 1911-1913 (Box-folder 249 / 4)
    - #1089 Detroit Copper Mining Company (Morenci, Arizona), 1909-1911 (Box-folder 249 / 5)
    - #1090 Miami Copper Company (Arizona), 1907-1911, 1948 (Box-folder 249 / 6)
    - #1091 Moctezuma Copper Company (Nacozari, Mexico), 1911 (Box-folder 249 / 7)
    - #1092 Utah Copper Company (Garfield, Utah), 1910-1930 (Box-folder 249 / 8)
    - #1093 International Smelting and Refining Company (Tooele, Utah), 1911-1965 (Box-folder 249 / 9)
    - #1093 International Smelting and Refining Company (Tooele, Utah): proposed slag treatment plant, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 249 / 10)
    - #1093 International Smelting and Refining Company (Tooele, Utah): proposed slag treatment plant, 1945-1969 (Box-folder 250 / 1-2)
    - #1094 American Smelting and Refining Company [ASARCO] (Garfield, Utah), 1910-1952 (Box-folder 250 / 3)
    - #1094 American Smelting and Refining Company [ASARCO] (Tacoma, Wash.), 1913-1970 (Box-folder 250 / 4)
    - #1094 American Smelting and Refining Company [ASARCO] (East Helena, Mont.) (re labor relations), 1938-1970 (Box-folder 250 / 5-6)
    - #1094 American Smelting and Refining Company [ASARCO], 1941-1965 (Box-folder 250 / 7)
    - #1095 Balaklala Consolidated Copper Company (Coram, Calif.), 1910 (Box-folder 250 / 8)
    - #1097 "Rental of A.C.M. Co.'s limestone lands: Montana City", 1911-1935 (Box-folder 250 / 9)
    - #1097-2 "Rental of A.C.M. Co.'s limestone lands: Goodman", 1911-1946 (Box-folder 250 / 10)
    - #1097-3 "Rental of A.C.M. Co.'s limestone lands: Doyle", 1915-1919 (Box-folder 250 / 11)
    - #1098 "Williams limestone properties at Albright, Montana", 1910-1912 (Box-folder 250 / 12)
    - #1099 "Albright quarries" (re construction and repair), 1910-1940 (Box-folder 250 / 13)
    - #1100 "General Office adjustments", 1910-1914 (Box-folder 251 / 1)
    - #1103 Engineering Department, 1912-1968 (Box-folder 251 / 2)
    - #1103-3 Engineering Department: engineering development, 1954-1969 (Box-folder 251 / 3)
    - #1103-5 Engineering Department: instrument department, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 251 / 4)
    - #1103-6 Engineering Department: maintenance, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 251 / 5)
    - #1104 "Hardinge Conical Pebble Mill", 1910-1939 (Box-folder 251 / 6)
    - #1104 "Hardinge Conical Pebble Mill" [Archives Map Case], 1910-1939 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1105 "Hardinge Conical Ball Mill", 1910-1927 (Box-folder 251 / 7)
    - #1106 Lochray Coal Company, 1912-1945 (Box-folder 251 / 8)
    - #1107 Unloading Department costs, 1907-1945 (Box-folder 251 / 9)
    - #1109 "Scrap wood", 1909-1962 (Box-folder 251 / 10)
    - #1110 "Construction and installation at Albright quarries: compressors", 1912-1914 (Box-folder 251 / 11)
    - #1110 "Construction and installation at Albright quarries: additional buildings", 1912-1914 (Box-folder 252 / 1)
    - #1110 Construction and installation at Albright quarries: additional buildings" [Archives Map Case], 1906-1911 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1111 "Soundings in blast furnace dust chamber", 1911-1953 (Box-folder 252 / 2)
    - #1112 "Measurement of flue gases", 1912 (Box-folder 252 / 3)
    - #1112 "Measurement of flue gases" [Archives Map Case], 1912 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1113 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #1", 1907 (Box-folder 252 / 4)
    - #1114 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #2", 1907-1909 (Box-folder 252 / 5)
    - #1114 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #2" [Archives Map Case], 1907-1909 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1115 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #3", 1907-1910 (Box-folder 252 / 6)
    - #1115 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #3" [Archives Map Case], 1907-1910 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1116 "Proposed new concentrator: estimate #4", 1907-1910 (Box-folder 252 / 7)
    - #1118 Canadian Copper Company (Ontario), 1911-1961 (Box-folder 252 / 8)
    - #1120 Construction Department, 1907-1968 (Box-folder 252 / 9-11)
    - #1121 "Plaster manufacture: gypsum plaster", 1910, 1958 (Box-folder 252 / 12)
    - #1122 Cerro de Pasco Mining Company (Peru), 1911-1956 (Box-folder 252 / 13)
    - #1123 "Slags: Wanjukoff investigation on loss of copper in slag in matte smelting", 1912 (Box-folder 253 / 1)
    - #1124 American Zinc Company, 1919-1970 (Box-folder 253 / 2)
    - #1125 Inspiration Copper Company, 1912-1970 (Box-folder 253 / 3)
    - #1126 "Collection of flue dust", 1909-1915 (Box-folder 253 / 4)
    - #1130 "Number of minutes required to finish a ton of copper" (sampled), 1914 (Box-folder 253 / 5)
    - #1131 "U.S. Government reports and statistics" (re production of limestone, accidents at Albright quarries), 1912-1945 (Box-folder 253 / 6)
    - #1133 "U.S. Government reports and statistics" (re brick, tile, and clay production), 1908-1939 (Box-folder 253 / 7)
    - #1134 Brick Department: annual report, 1912 (Box-folder 253 / 8)
    - #1135 Boiler Shop (includes material on fires of January 1926 and April 1949), 1913-1949 (Box-folder 253 / 9)
    - #1135 Boiler Shop: labor troubles, 1918-1959 (Box-folder 253 / 10)
    - #1136-1 "A.C.M. Co.: Great Falls Reduction Department" (re requests for information), 1954-1968 (Box-folder 253 / 11)
    - #1136-3 "A.C.M. Co.: manufacture of phosphate at Anaconda", 1920-1961 (Box-folder 253 / 12)
    - #1136-5 "A.C.M. Co.: family day", 1956-1959 (Box-folder 253 / 13)
    - #1136-6 "A.C.M. Co.: managers meetings", 1957-1963 (Box-folder 254 / 1-7)
    - #1136-6 "A.C.M. Co.: managers meetings", 1964-1968 (Box-folder 255 / 1-4)
    - #1137 Brick Department: construction and installation, 1912-1922 (Box-folder 255 / 5)
    - #1139 Arsenic Plant, 1912-1916 (Box-folder 255 / 6)
    - #1140-3 "Dwight-Lloyd sintering furnace: tests of G.F. products at East Helena", 1909-1924 (Box-folder 255 / 7)
    - #1140-4 "Dwight-Lloyd sintering furnace: proposed installation at Great Falls", 1909-1924 (Box-folder 255 / 8)
    - #1140 "Dwight-Lloyd sintering furnace: proposed installation at Great Falls" [Archives Map Case], 1909-1924 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1140-5 "Dwight-Lloyd sintering furnace: sintering test on rhodochrosite ore", 1920-1923 (Box-folder 255 / 9)
    - #1141 "Sintering test at Great Falls", 1910-1913 (Box-folder 256 / 1)
    - #1142 "Treatment of flue dust" (re processes for extraction of arsenic and bismuth), 1903-1915 (Box-folder 256 / 2)
    - #1145 "Special investigations re quality of copper", 1909-1964 (Box-folder 256 / 3)
    - #1145-7 "Special investigations re quality of copper: annealing temperatures and effect...on conductivity, torsion, tensile strength, and elongation", 1907-1920 (Box-folder 256 / 4)
    - #1145-8 "Special investigations re quality of copper: effect of casting methods and casting temperature on conductivity", 1910-1928 (Box-folder 256 / 5)
    - #1145-9 "Special investigations re quality of copper: structure and properties of copper", 1918-1932 (Box-folder 256 / 6)
    - #1145-10 "Special investigations re quality of copper: products of Ansonia and Great Falls mills", 1923-1963 (Box-folder 256 / 7)
    - #1149 Builders' Exchange, 1913, 1930 (Box-folder 256 / 8)
    - #1150 "Hospitals and doctors" (re leaves, complaints), 1897-1953 (Box-folder 256 / 9)
    - #1152 "Wheeler-Krejci patent on process of forming magnetite coating for furnace linings", 1912-1915 (Box-folder 256 / 10)
    - #1152 "Wheeler-Krejci patent on process of forming magnetite coating for furnace linings" [Archives Map Case], 1912-1915 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1156 Mt. Lyell Mining and Railway Company, Ltd. (Tasmania), 1913-1930 (Box-folder 256 / 11)
    - #1157 American Institute of Mining Engineers (includes papers re Great Falls Reduction Dept.), 1913-1959 (Box-folder 256 / 12-14)
    - #1157 American Institute of Mining Engineers (includes papers re Great Falls Reduction Department), 1960-1970 (Box-folder 257 / 1)
    - #1157-4 American Institute of Mining Engineers: James Douglas Medal, 1923-1945 (Box-folder 257 / 2)
    - #1160 Brick Department: test series 145, 1913 (Box-folder 257 / 3)
    - #1160 "Brick Department: test series 145" [Archives Map Case], 1913 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1161 "Oil and gas resources of Montana and Alberta: natural gas well at Havre", 1913-1949 (Box-folder 257 / 4)
    - #1161 "Oil and gas resources of Montana and Alberta: use of natural gas at Great Falls plant", 1925-1959 (Box-folder 257 / 5-8)
    - #1162 "Taxes on Albright quarries property", 1906-1966 (Box-folder 257 / 9)
    - #1165 Crushing Plant (re cost of crushing limestone at Great Falls and Albright; construction and installation), 1913-1928 (Box-folder 257 / 10)
    - #1166 "Diamond drilling", 1913-1914 (Box-folder 258 / 1)
    - #1168 "Shipment of employees' household goods", 1920-1929 (Box-folder 258 / 2)
    - #1169 Electric Tramming Department, 1913-1970 (Box-folder 258 / 3)
    - #1177 "Tests: various coals in furnace refining Diamondville coal dust vs. Lochray coal dust", 1923-1932 (Box-folder 258 / 4)
    - #1186 Arsenic Plant, 1913-1918 (Box-folder 258 / 5)
    - #1186-2 Arsenic Plant: damage from arsenical poison, 1916-1950 (Box-folder 258 / 6)
    - #1186-3 Arsenic Plant: test series 246, 1913-1938 (Box-folder 258 / 7)
    - #1186-3 Arsenic Plant: test series 246 [Archives Map Case], 1913-1938 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1187 Metallurgical plants: Raritan Copper Works, 1932-1969 (Box-folder 258 / 8-10)
    - #1187 Metallurgical plants: Raritan Copper Works (re baghouse fume treatment), 1934-1944 (Box-folder 258 / 11)
    - #1187 Metallurgical plants, 1917-1957 (Box-folder 258 / 12)
    - #1187-9 Metallurgical plants: zinc, 1919-1959 (Box-folder 258 / 13-14)
    - #1187-9 Metallurgical plants: zinc, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 259 / 1)
    - #1187 Metallurgical plants, 1925-1946 (Box-folder 259 / 2)
    - #1187-9 Metallurgical plants [Archives Map Case], 1925-1946 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1187-14 Metallurgical plants: Consolidated Mining and Smelting Company (Trail, B.C.), 1917-1967 (Box-folder 259 / 3)
    - #1187-15 Metallurgical plants: Bunker Hill and Sullivan Mining and Concentrating Company, 1921-1973 (Box-folder 259 / 4)
    - #1187-17 Metallurgical plants: American Zinc Oxide Company, 1926 (Box-folder 259 / 5)
    - #1187-17 Metallurgical plants: American Zinc Oxide Company [Archives Map Case], 1926 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1187-23 Metallurgical plants: Cobre de Mexico Copper Refinery, 1948-1966 (Box-folder 259 / 6)
    - #1189 "Store rooms: records room for storage of files and records", 1914-1927 (Box-folder 259 / 7)
    - #1194 "Flotation", 1912-1921 (Box-folder 259 / 8)
    - #1194 "Flotation" [Archives Map Case], 1912-1921 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1195 Safety First Department: monthly accident reports, 1941-1968 (Box-folder 260 / 1-5)
    - #1196 "Treatment of Butte ores: cost & recovery reports", 1912-1924 (Box-folder 260 / 6)
    - #1196 "Treatment of Butte ores: cost & recovery reports" [Archives Map Case], 1912-1924 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1201 "Treatment of stockpile slime", 1914 (Box-folder 260 / 7)
    - #1202 "Laist leaching process", 1913 (Box-folder 260 / 8)
    - #1203 "Libby-Krejci leaching process", 1913-1914 (Box-folder 260 / 9)
    - #1203 "Libby-Krejci leaching process" [Archives Map Case], 1913-14 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - #1206 Slime Flotation Plant, 1915-1925 (Box-folder 260 / 10)
    - #1208 "Klepinger-Krejci-Kuzell process of smelting fine concentrates", 1914-1931 (Box-folder 260 / 11)
    - #1209 "Coal dust firing for refining furnaces", 1915-1930 (Box-folder 261 / 1)
    - #1209 "Coal dust firing for refining furnaces" [Archives Map Case], 1915-1930 (Oversize-folder 5)
    - #1210 "Investigations of Smoke Commission re elimination of sulphur & arsenic from flue gases & flue dust" (re air pollution), 1911-1970 (Box-folder 261 / 2)
    - #1210-2 "Investigations of Smoke Commission re elimination of sulphur & arsenic from flue gases & flue dust: sampling flue gases under...Dr. Cottrell" (re air pollution), 1911-1919 (Box-folder 261 / 3)
    - #1210-3 "Investigations of Smoke Commission re elimination of sulphur & arsenic from flue gases & flue dust: Kelley, Thiogen and Reed processes" (re air pollution), 1909-1912 (Box-folder 261 / 4)
    - #1210-4 "Investigations of Smoke Commission re elimination of sulphur & arsenic from flue gases & flue dust: H. Hass' process for sulphur recovery" (re air pollution), 1914 (Box-folder 261 / 5)
    - #1210-5 "Investigations of Smoke Commission re elimination of sulphur & arsenic from flue gases & flue dust: recommendations for improved Arsenic Plant operation at Washoe" (re air pollution), 1913 (Box-folder 261 / 6)
    - #1211-1212 "Volume, solid content, draft, velocity, & temperatures of gases in connecting flue of new flue system: test #105" [and test 130], 1911-1915 (Box-folder 261 / 7-9)
    - #1212 "Volume, solid content, draft, velocity, & temperatures of gases in connecting flue of new flue system: test #105" [Archives Map Case], 1911-1915 (Oversize-folder 5)
    - #1212 "Volume, solid content, draft, velocity, & temperatures of gases in connecting flue of new flue system: test #130", 1912 (Box-folder 262 / 1)
    - #1213 "Thawing shed: damage to railroad cars", 1914-1915 (Box-folder 262 / 2)
    - #1214 "Great Falls water supply: investigation re...Giant Springs as possible supply", 1912-1941 (Box-folder 262 / 3)
    - #1214 "Great Falls water supply: proposal to extend city ... water to smelter", 1913-1920 (Box-folder 262 / 4)
    - #1214 "Great Falls water supply: distribution to departments", 1932-1959 (Box-folder 262 / 5)
    - #1215 "Check assays on Anaconda anodes shipped to Rariton", 1915-1916 (Box-folder 262 / 6)
    - #1216 "Corrosion of iron & steel", 1912 (Box-folder 262 / 7)
    - #1217 "Tracy billet mould", 1914-1917 (Box-folder 262 / 8)
    - #1219 "Anode shipments from Washoe Reduction Works", 1915-1959 (Box-folder 262 / 9)
    - #1219-2 "Anode shipments from Washoe Reduction Works: analyses of anodes", 1918-1958 (Box-folder 262 / 10)
    - #1221 "Refining of high arsenic anodes...", 1911-1952 (Box-folder 262 / 11)
    - #1221 "Refining of high arsenic anodes...: preparation of impure anodes", 1911-1948 (Box-folder 262 / 12)
    - #1222 "Arsenic and antimony in Anaconda refined anodes", 1915-1963 (Box-folder 262 / 13)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department, 1908-1955 (Box-folder 262 / 14-15)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 263 / 1)
    - #1223-3 "Rolling Mills Department: construction and installation of rod and wire mill", 1917-1957 (Box-folder 263 / 2)
    - #1223-4 "Rolling Mills Department: power contract with Montana Power Company", 1919-1960 (Box-folder 263 / 3)
    - #1223-5 "Rolling Mills Department: construction of office and change house", 1918-1965 (Box-folder 263 / 4)
    - #1223-8 "Rolling Mills Department: wire drawing machines", 1918-1956 (Box-folder 263 / 5)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department [miscellaneous files], 1918-1922 (Box-folder 263 / 6)
    - #1223-20 "Rolling Mills Department: proposed rod & wire mill...to increase capacity", 1919-1921 (Box-folder 263 / 7)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department [miscellaneous files], 1919-1950 (Box-folder 263 / 8)
    - #1223-34 "Rolling Mills Department: seniority & promotion of employees", 1920-1965 (Box-folder 263 / 9)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department [miscellaneous files], 1920-1961 (Box-folder 263 / 10)
    - #1223-46 "Rolling Mills Department: dies", 1913-1948 (Box-folder 264 / 1)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department [miscellaneous files], 1920-1924 (Box-folder 264 / 2)
    - #1223-92 "Rolling Mills Department: savings", 1929-1958 (Box-folder 264 / 3)
    - #1223-96 "Rolling Mills Department: Great Falls business statements", 1933-1946 (Box-folder 264 / 4)
    - #1223 Rolling Mills Department [miscellaneous files], 1936-1965 (Box-folder 264 / 5)
    - #1223-102 "Rolling Mills Department: changes & improvements at Great Falls", 1939-1960 (Box-folder 264 / 6-7)
    - #1223-102 "Rolling Mills Department: changes & improvements at Great Falls" [Archives Map Case], 1939-1960 (Oversize-folder 5)
    - #1223-103 "Rolling Mills Department: conferences between shop stewards & management", 1943-1959 (Box-folder 264 / 8)